{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "4√(14)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(14) - 2√(14).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 2 \u003d 4\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(504) - √(56)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(2) - 3√(2).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 3 \u003d 3\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(72) - √(18)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(2) + 3√(2).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 3 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(72) + √(18)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 4√(2) - 2√(2).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n4 - 2 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(32) - √(8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(11)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(11) + 4√(11).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 4 \u003d 6\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(44) + √(176)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(2) + 4√(2).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 4 \u003d 10\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(72) + √(32)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2√(13)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(13) - 4√(13).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 - 4 \u003d -2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(52) - √(208)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(15) + 3√(15).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 3 \u003d 5\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(60) + √(135)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 4√(15) + 3√(15).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n4 + 3 \u003d 7\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(240) + √(135)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-√(6)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(6) - 3√(6).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 - 3 \u003d -1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(24) - √(54)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 12√(3) + 2√(3).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n12 + 2 \u003d 14\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(432) + √(12)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(11)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(11) + 2√(11).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 + 2 \u003d 7\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(275) + √(44)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(2) + 3√(2).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 3 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(72) + √(18)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(17) + 4√(17).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 4 \u003d 6\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(68) + √(272)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-√(21)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(21) - 4√(21).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 - 4 \u003d -1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(189) - √(336)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8√(11)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(11) + 2√(11).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 2 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(396) + √(44)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(17) + 3√(17).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 + 3 \u003d 6\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(153) + √(153)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6 + 2.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 2 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36) + √(4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 10√(5) - 4√(5).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n10 - 4 \u003d 6\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(500) - √(80)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6 + 3.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 3 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36) + √(9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(14)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(14) - 3√(14).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 3 \u003d 3\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(504) - √(126)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8√(6)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(6) + 2√(6).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 2 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(216) + √(24)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(7)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(7) + 4√(7).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 + 4 \u003d 7\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(63) + √(112)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(19)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 4√(19) + 2√(19).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n4 + 2 \u003d 6\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(304) + √(76)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6 + 2.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 2 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36) + √(4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 10√(3) - 4√(3).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n10 - 4 \u003d 6\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(300) - √(48)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-√(7)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(7) - 4√(7).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 - 4 \u003d -1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(63) - √(112)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(14)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(14) - 4√(14).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 4 \u003d 1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(350) - √(224)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9√(11)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(11) + 4√(11).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 + 4 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(275) + √(176)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 9 - 4.\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n9 - 4 \u003d 5\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81) - √(16)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4√(11)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(11) + 2√(11).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 2 \u003d 4\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(44) + √(44)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(15) + 2√(15).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 + 2 \u003d 5\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(135) + √(60)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(11)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(11) - 3√(11).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 3 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(275) - √(99)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(2) + 4√(2).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 4 \u003d 6\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(8) + √(32)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(2) - 4√(2).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 4 \u003d 1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(50) - √(32)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 4√(3) + 3√(3).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n4 + 3 \u003d 7\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(48) + √(27)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 12 - 2.\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n12 - 2 \u003d 10\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(144) - √(4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(5) + 3√(5).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 + 3 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(125) + √(45)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(21)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(21) - 4√(21).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 4 \u003d 1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(525) - √(336)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "21√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 18√(2) + 3√(2).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n18 + 3 \u003d 21\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(648) + √(18)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6 + 2.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 2 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36) + √(4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 8√(3) + 3√(3).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n8 + 3 \u003d 11\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(192) + √(27)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 18 - 4.\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n18 - 4 \u003d 14\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(324) - √(16)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(3) - 4√(3).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 4 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(108) - √(48)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(3) + 2√(3).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 2 \u003d 4\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(12) + √(12)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5√(7)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(7) + 2√(7).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 + 2 \u003d 5\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(63) + √(28)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(5) - 3√(5).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 - 3 \u003d -1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(20) - √(45)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 8 + 4.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n8 + 4 \u003d 12\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64) + √(16)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(3) - 2√(3).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 2 \u003d 4\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(108) - √(12)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 8 + 4.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n8 + 4 \u003d 12\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64) + √(16)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(10)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(10) - 3√(10).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 3 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(250) - √(90)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 4√(5) + 4√(5).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n4 + 4 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(80) + √(80)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(17) - 3√(17).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 3 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(425) - √(153)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(13)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(13) - 2√(13).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 2 \u003d 3\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(325) - √(52)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 8 + 2.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n8 + 2 \u003d 10\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(64) + √(4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(15) - 4√(15).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 4 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(540) - √(240)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(5) - 4√(5).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 4 \u003d 1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(125) - √(80)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 10 + 4.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n10 + 4 \u003d 14\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100) + √(16)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(15) + 4√(15).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 + 4 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(375) + √(240)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(17) + 2√(17).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 + 2 \u003d 5\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(153) + √(68)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4√(19)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(19) + 2√(19).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 2 \u003d 4\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(76) + √(76)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 4√(17) + 4√(17).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n4 + 4 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(272) + √(272)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(17) + 2√(17).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 + 2 \u003d 7\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(425) + √(68)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 10 - 2.\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n10 - 2 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(100) - √(4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4√(21)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(21) - 2√(21).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 2 \u003d 4\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(756) - √(84)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(7)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(7) + 2√(7).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 + 2 \u003d 7\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(175) + √(28)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2√(19)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(19) - 4√(19).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 - 4 \u003d -2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(76) - √(304)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 12√(5) - 2√(5).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n12 - 2 \u003d 10\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(720) - √(20)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "18", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 20 - 2.\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n20 - 2 \u003d 18\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(400) - √(4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(15) - 4√(15).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 4 \u003d 1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(375) - √(240)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(17) - 3√(17).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 3 \u003d 3\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(612) - √(153)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 9 + 4.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n9 + 4 \u003d 13\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(81) + √(16)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6 + 3.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 3 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36) + √(9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(15) + 2√(15).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 + 2 \u003d 7\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(375) + √(60)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 8√(5) + 3√(5).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n8 + 3 \u003d 11\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(320) + √(45)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(19)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(19) - 3√(19).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 3 \u003d 3\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(684) - √(171)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3√(7)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(7) - 3√(7).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 3 \u003d 3\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(252) - √(63)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(15) + 4√(15).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 4 \u003d 10\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(540) + √(240)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 10√(3) + 4√(3).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n10 + 4 \u003d 14\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(300) + √(48)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(15) - 4√(15).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 4 \u003d 1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(375) - √(240)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(21)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(21) - 3√(21).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 3 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(525) - √(189)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 4√(17) + 4√(17).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n4 + 4 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(272) + √(272)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "√(7)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(7) - 2√(7).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 - 2 \u003d 1\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(63) - √(28)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6 + 2.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 2 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(36) + √(4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "14√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 12√(2) + 2√(2).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n12 + 2 \u003d 14\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(288) + √(8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "23", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 20 + 3.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n20 + 3 \u003d 23\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(400) + √(9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(17)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(17) - 4√(17).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 - 4 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(612) - √(272)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5√(10)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(10) + 2√(10).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 + 2 \u003d 5\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(90) + √(40)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 6√(2) + 3√(2).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n6 + 3 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(72) + √(18)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8√(15)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(15) + 3√(15).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 + 3 \u003d 8\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(375) + √(135)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 12√(2) - 3√(2).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n12 - 3 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(288) - √(18)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "21√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 18√(2) + 3√(2).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n18 + 3 \u003d 21\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(648) + √(18)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4√(13)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(13) + 2√(13).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 2 \u003d 4\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(52) + √(52)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2√(3)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 5√(3) - 3√(3).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n5 - 3 \u003d 2\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(75) - √(27)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10√(2)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 12√(2) - 2√(2).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n12 - 2 \u003d 10\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(288) - √(8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6√(13)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 3√(13) + 3√(13).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n3 + 3 \u003d 6\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(117) + √(117)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5√(11)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 2√(11) + 3√(11).\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n2 + 3 \u003d 5\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(44) + √(99)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7√(5)", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 10√(5) - 3√(5).\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n10 - 3 \u003d 7\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(500) - √(45)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 12 - 3.\nThen subtract the rational part of the two radicals.\n12 - 3 \u003d 9\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(144) - √(9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15", "explanation": "Start by simplifying both the radicals so that the radicand may be equal and we can join the rational parts of the radicals.\nYou will have 12 + 3.\nThen add the rational part of the two radicals.\n12 + 3 \u003d 15\nPut the resulting rational number with the square root to get the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n√(144) + √(9)", "type": "text"}
]}